Hello everyone and welcome to this new video!
I thought I'll do another shoe video, maybe you remember my last time I tried to walk in weird shoes
I think it was Bella Tears from Jell-O-I
So today I have something new
It's called Pony Boots
And I chose a really fun colour because I thought, well let's do not wear something black this time
time but this cool holographic blue and I had a lot of space around me so I'll see how I'm going to
do these shoes compared to the last time I totally fit so this will be my first time let's try this
The first thing I have to say is that they look really awesome with the color.
It is really like bam and bright blue.
Really love the look.
My toes don't hurt yet, which is really a good sign.
Yeah, I feel like I have enough place for my toes and my feet in there and that I could
like wear them while I'm sitting forever. The only thing I noticed is that they
don't have heels here so I kind of have to put my feet in a way that they're not
falling back or something because then it really looks weird and feels weird.
So you have to balance it a bit due to the missing heel.
Okay, let's try to stand up and see how it works.
Okay, I'm standing.
I feel like I constantly have to be on my toes to gain my balance but it is doable.
I think it's better than with the buttered heels last time.
I have to keep moving and it's pretty exhausting for my legs, I can already feel that.
But I feel like it's doable, so I try to keep in motion.
Giving my legs a moment of rest, but that went rather well I would say.
so let's try something more difficult and let's do some stairs
Luckily I can hold on to the sides here to stabilize myself a bit.
That went rather well. I have to say I didn't expect it to be that easy to walk in them.
So all good I guess. I think the secret is really to constantly be in motion and walk
walk around, be moving because then you have a better balance feeling so to say. They're definitely
not something for a nice walk in the forest or something relaxing because it is rather exhausting
without the heel. But I still really really love the color and that is the cool thing about Jalawai
that you have a huge range of colors. You can order the shoes in all different kind of colors
for example these blue ones or and I have a second pair yellow metallic snake print
because I thought well I have so many shoes but what are the colors I do not own in shoes yet and
I came up with yellow and blue and I think these are going to be a bit more relaxing because they
do have a heel so I'm going to change into them now as well.
These are a bit easier to wear, more comfortable for the heels to just relax them.
but I have to say they're a bit too big I ordered both in size 40 and these do fit
perfectly so I felt really comfortable and secure in them while walking these are a bit too
large but it's okay I think when I stand up I'll slide a bit in them and one thing I
noticed is that you can't just set them up so well because they are falling. So you have to figure out how to store them.
Like this for example. As I thought in general they were comfortable but yeah they did fit better.
Okay so which one do you like more? Did you ever try N-Walk and Pony boots? Let me
know in the comments down below and subscribe to my channel if you like this video.
I hope you had a nice time, see you around, bye!